<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Printer Archives - technoMarket</title>
	<atom:link href="https://soumayaakil.github.io/market/product-category/printer/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://soumayaakil.github.io/market/product-category/printer/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 08:30:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Gold Sprocket &#8211; Photo personal Printer</title>
		<link>https://soumayaakil.github.io/market/product/gold-sprocket-photo-personal-printer/</link>
					<comments>https://soumayaakil.github.io/market/product/gold-sprocket-photo-personal-printer/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[techno]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 07:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo2.transvelo.in/techmarket/?post_type=product&#038;p=709</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Live it - Love it - Print it: Printing off social media photos has never been easier from your smartphone. Connect your social media accounts to the free-to-download HP Sprocket App and instantly turn those photos into colorful prints</li>
<li>A Social on-the-go portable printer: Sprocket uses seamless Bluetooth connectivity, so you can set it up at parties and events, and everyone can print their favorite moments from their smartphones or tablets</li>
<li>Have fun - be creative: Customize your photos before you print with the HP Sprocket App to add fun text, borders, emojis, and more. Add a pop of personality for snapshots and stickers that are totally and uniquely you</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://soumayaakil.github.io/market/product/gold-sprocket-photo-personal-printer/">Gold Sprocket &#8211; Photo personal Printer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://soumayaakil.github.io/market">technoMarket</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Live it &#8211; Love it &#8211; Print it: Printing off social media photos has never been easier from your smartphone. Connect your social media accounts to the free-to-download HP Sprocket App and instantly turn those photos into colorful prints</li>
<li>A Social on-the-go portable printer: Sprocket uses seamless Bluetooth connectivity, so you can set it up at parties and events, and everyone can print their favorite moments from their smartphones or tablets</li>
<li>Have fun &#8211; be creative: Customize your photos before you print with the HP Sprocket App to add fun text, borders, emojis, and more. Add a pop of personality for snapshots and stickers that are totally and uniquely you</li>
<li>Instant snapshots anywhere: This compact photo printer was made to go wherever you do. It easily fits into any bag, so you can create 2&#215;3-inch stickable snapshots whenever the moment strikes</li>
<li>How to print: Connect the Sprocket Photo Printer to your mobile device via Bluetooth. Download the free and easy-to-use HP Sprocket App and enjoy fun portable printing</li>
<li>For best results, use Original HP ZINK sticky-backed photo Paper: it’s specially designed to ensure you get bright, glossy photos with vibrant colors every time you print. Just peel off the back of your prints and your photos become instant stickers</li>
<li>Main functions of the Sprocket portable photo printer: 2&#215;3 photo printing on sticky-backed paper, mobile printing &#8211; take it anywhere, social media printing &#8211; print photos from your social media profiles, Bluetooth smartphone connectivity, and more</li>
<li>One-year limited hardware warranty; 24-hour, 7 days a week Web support</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://soumayaakil.github.io/market/product/gold-sprocket-photo-personal-printer/">Gold Sprocket &#8211; Photo personal Printer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://soumayaakil.github.io/market">technoMarket</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://soumayaakil.github.io/market/product/gold-sprocket-photo-personal-printer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
